(Howard:)For this, I went to MIT.
(Sheldon:)And begin.
[GRUNTING & GAGGING]
(Raj:)I think I swallowed some paint.
(Leonard:)I can't press any of the buttons
with my gloves.
(Leonard:)Oh, son of a bitch.
(Sheldon:)Adversity is to be expected. Continue.
[BUZZ]
(Howard:)Oh, boy, am I gonna get sued.
- Okay, I can't do this.
- Me either.
(Sheldon:)Gentlemen, use your imagination.
Innovate.
(Sheldon:)Did Han Solo let Luke Skywalker freeze
to death on the ice planet of Hoth?
(Sheldon:)No, he cut open a tauntaun and used
its internal body heat to warm him up.
(Howard:)You heard the man.
Hold him down and I'll cut him open.
(Leonard:)Hang on. I know I don't possess the tools
of leadership, but I don't understand...
(Leonard:)...why we can't assemble the equipment
inside the hut and then take it outside.
(Sheldon:)I hadn't thought of that.